Privacy Policy

US State Privacy Notices

Make a Privacy Request

Our Privacy Policy
==================

Last Updated: Jun 4, 2024

Expand All

Information you provide to us

We collect the personal information you provide to us when you purchase our products or visit our website. The categories of information we may collect include:

* Personal Identifiers, including name, email address, postal address, telephone number, and online Identifiers
* Internet Activity
* Commercial Information, including purchases
* Financial Information, including credit or debit card number
* Location Information, including general location data
* Inferences from Other Data, including inferences created from other personal information collected

### Browser Cookies

We use cookies to create a better experience for you on our site. For example, cookies prevent you from having to login repeatedly, and they help us remember items you've added to your cart. We also use third-party cookies, which are cookies placed by third parties for advertising and analytics purposes. You can control these cookies through your browser settings.

### How long we keep your data

We do not retain data for any longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this Policy.

We generally retain data according to the guidelines below.

| Type of Data | Retention Period |
| --- | --- |
| Cookies and online data we collect while you use our website, including Internet Activity, General location data | We delete or anonymize data concerning your use of our website within 10 years of collecting it. |
| Data we collect in order to process and ship orders you place with us, including Name, Email address, Postal address, Telephone number, Internet Activity, Purchases, Credit or debit card number, General location data | We keep personal information related to products and services you purchase for as long as the personal data is required for us to fulfill our contract with you, and for 10 years from your last purchase with us. We may keep data beyond this period in anonymized form. |
| Data we collect when you contact us for customer support and other inquiries, including Name, Email address, Telephone number | We keep customer feedback and correspondence with our customer service for up to 10 years to help us respond to any questions or complaints. We may keep data beyond this period in anonymized form. |
| Data we collect when you sign up for promotional and marketing communications, including Name, Email address, Online Identifiers, Internet Activity, Inferences created from other personal information collected | Where you have signed up to receive promotional and marketing communications from us, we will retain any data collected until you opt out or request its deletion. We may keep data beyond this period in anonymized form. We will further retain a record of any opt-outs in order to prevent sending you future communications. |
| Data we collect when you review our products, answer surveys, or send feedback, including Name, Email address, Internet Activity | We retain review, survey, and feedback data for up to 10 years following your last contact with us. We may keep data beyond this period in anonymized form to help improve our products and services. |
| Data we collect in connection with privacy requests, including Name, Email address, Postal address, Telephone number | We retain records related to privacy requests as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, and for a minimum of 24 months. |
| Data we collect for security purposes, including Name, Email address, Postal address, Telephone number | We retain security-related data as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations and to maintain and improve our information security measures. |

### Why we process your information

We process personal information for the following business and commercial purposes:

* Analyzing Data
* Conducting Surveys
* Creating Customer Profiles
* Delivering Targeted Ads
* Fulfilling Customer Orders
* Improving our Products & Services
* Internal Business Operations
* Marketing Our Products & Services
* Meeting Compliance & Legal Requirements
* Operating Our Website or Mobile Apps
* Preventing Fraud
* Processing Payments
* Providing Customer Support
* Providing Cybersecurity
* Sending Promotional Communications
* Storing and Managing Data
* Tracking Purchases & Customer Data

How we disclose your information

We may disclose personal information about you for business and commercial purposes when you purchase our products or visit our website:

| Personal Information Category | Categories of Service Providers | Categories of Third Parties |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Personal Identifiers | Commerce Software Tools, Governance, Risk & Compliance Software, IT Infrastructure Services, Payment Processors, Sales & Marketing Tools, and Shipping Services | Ad Networks, Business Operations Tool, Commerce Software Tools, Data Analytics Providers, Payment Processors, and Shipping Services |
| Internet Activity | Commerce Software Tools, IT Infrastructure Services, Payment Processors, and Sales & Marketing Tools | Ad Networks, Commerce Software Tools, Data Analytics Providers, and Payment Processors |
| Commercial Information | Commerce Software Tools, IT Infrastructure Services, Payment Processors, and Sales & Marketing Tools | Ad Networks, Business Operations Tool, Commerce Software Tools, and Payment Processors |
| Financial Information | Commerce Software Tools, IT Infrastructure Services, Payment Processors, and Sales & Marketing Tools | Business Operations Tool, Commerce Software Tools, and Payment Processors |
| Location Information | IT Infrastructure Services and Sales & Marketing Tools | Ad Networks, Commerce Software Tools, Data Analytics Providers, and Payment Processors |
| Inferences from Other Data | IT Infrastructure Services and Sales & Marketing Tools | Ad Networks |

* * *

Powered by[](https://www.truevault.com/)
